(Sheldon:)Specifically, how would the Civil War
have gone differently...
(Sheldon:)...if Lincoln had been
a robot sent from the future?
(Sheldon:)Look at that, there's even pasta left over.
(Leonard:)Do you understand
that this was supposed to be a date?
(Sheldon:)I do. Do you?
(Sheldon:)Because, frankly, you've been
in a foul mood since I sat down.
Okay, here's my question:
(Leonard:)Why did you sit down?
(Sheldon:)To help.
Look, if you fail at this relationship...
(Sheldon:)...and history suggests you will...
(Sheldon:)...then we risk losing the medical officer
that our landing party has always needed.
(Leonard:)What landing party?
(Sheldon:)You're Kirk. I'm Spock.
Wolowitz is Scotty.
(Sheldon:)Koothrappali is the guy
who always gets killed.
(Sheldon:)And now we've got McCoy.